我将去往南方公园 度过一段时光
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
处处是无欲谦人 友善面庞
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
我将去往南方公园 远离我的悲伤
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
日夜都有充足车位 邻居人人礼貌大方
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
我将去往南方公园 试着放松一场
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
我爱女孩 大奶成双
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
快来南方公园吧 与我的朋友会一场
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
南方公园 第11季第1季 "向Jackson神父的道歉"
Episode 11x01 "With Apologies To Jesse Jackson"
现在回到《财富轮盘》
And now back to, Wheel of Fortune.
好了 Randy 恭喜你一直晋级到这一轮
Allright, Randy. Congratulations on making it all the way to the bonus round.
-谢谢你 Pat -你有家人今晚一直在这里？
Thanks, Pat. - You got some family here watching tonight.
对 他们都支持我
Yeah, they're all rooting for me.
我相信肯定有很多朋友在家里看着
And I'm sure you have lots of friends watching back home?
对 你们好 南方公园看电视的大家
Yeah. Hi, everybody watching in South Park.
-说的是我们！ -祝你好运！
That's us. - Good luck!
好 让我们看看你能不能让每个人感到骄傲
Well let see if you can make everyone proud.
类别是“你讨厌的人”
The category is: "People who annoy you."
好的
Okay.
如往常一样 我们给你字母 "R" "T" "S" "L" 和"E"
As always we give you the letters, "R", "T", "S", "L" and "E".
我们只需要另外三个辅音和一个元音
We just need three more consonants and a vowel.
好的 我要一个“B”
Okay, I'd like a "B".
一个"N"和一个"G"
A "N" and a "G".
-元音呢？ -请给一个"O"
And the vowel? - An "O", please.
好的 看上去你获得的帮助不少
Okay well, looks like you're gonna get a lot of help here.
类别是“你讨厌的人” 观众请保持安静
The category is: "People who annoy you." Audience keep quiet please.
呃...
Uh...
嗯 呃...
Well, uhm...
十秒钟 Marsh先生
Ten seconds, Mr. Marsh.
-我知道这个词 但是我觉得不应该说 -五秒钟 Marsh先生
I know it, but I don't think I should say it. - Five seconds, Mr. Marsh.
好的 我想解这个字谜
Allright, I'd like to solve the puzzle.
Niggers.
哦 Naggers（唠叨鬼） 当然 Naggers 是啊
Oh, naggers, of course. Naggers. Right.
呃 我们能切掉...
Uh, can we cut to a...
我们能不能切掉...
Could we cut to a-
嗯 我努力猜了
Well, I gave it my best shot.
至少我们有了一次有趣的旅行 是吗 大伙？
At least we had a fup trip, huh gang?
我不敢相信你居然在全国电视上说了“N”字
I can't believe you said the "N" word on national television.
什么？
What?
为什么 我该说什么 Sharon？ 我以为我能拿到3万块！
Well, what i was supposed to do, Sharon? I thought I was gonna make $30.000!
Stanley老爸说这个词的唯一原因 就是他以为他能赢钱！
Stanley, the only reason daddy used that word, is that he thought he would win money!
老兄 你爸爸知道这个节目是现场直播吗？
Dude, did your dad know the show was being broadcast live?
老兄 这是我见过最有趣的事了 我在YouTube上看了不下60次
Dude, the funniest thing I've ever seen. I watched it on YouTube about 60 times.
我们能不能不谈这个 拜托？ 我不像谈这个
Can we just drop this, please? I don't wanna talk about it.
好啊 你需要担心的可不是我们
Yeah, well, it's not us you have to worry about.
而是Token
It's Token.
-他会把你打得满地找牙 -他不会的 他会吗？
He is gonna wanna kick your cracker teeth in. - No, he's not. Is he?
-我不知道 -我只需要解释一下
I don't know. - I just need to explain things.
嗨 Token
Hey, Token.
听着 我不知道你昨晚有没有看财富轮盘 但是...
Look, I don't know if you saw Wheel of Fortune last night, but...
是的 我们全家一起看了
Yeah, I was watching with my whole family.
然后我们今早在新闻里看了所有的重播
And then we saw all the replays this morning on the news.
听着 Token 我爸爸不是种族分子 他只是犯傻了 好不好？
Listen, Token, my dad isn't an racist. He's just stupid, allright?
他只是脱口而出那个"N"字 没什么大不了的 对吧？
He just blurted out the "N" word, and it's no big deal, okay?
哦 嗯 事实上这有什么大不了的 Stan
Uh, well, actually it is kinda a big deal, Stan.
这可能是个错误 但你不明白听到这个字是什么感觉
It may be a mistake, but you don't understand how it feels when that word comes up.
所以不要说没什么大不了的
So don't say it isn't a big deal.
哦 狗屎 快来看啊 打起来了 种族战争
Oh, shit, here we go. It's on! Race war!
种族战争！种族战争！
Race war! Race war!
大家看 种族战争打起来啦！ 就要开打啦！就要开打啦！
Race war is on, everybody! It's going down! Shit is going down!
Token 我爸爸没想冒犯 就让这事儿过去吧
Token my dad wasn't trying to be offensive, just forget about it.
-你说起来倒是容易 Stan -好啊 快点 快打啊！
That's easy for you to say, Stan. - Yeah, come on. Here we go!
对 但他没有含恨或在类似情绪下说那个字
Yeah, but he didn't say it in anger or anything like that.
-那样不代表我就觉得没事了 -种族战争 快点 种族战争！
That doesn't mean I can just be fine. - Race war, come on. Race war!
如果你真的觉得没什么大不了 那你就真的很无知
If you really think it's not a big deal, then you really are ignorant.
就这样 我不会跟任何人打架
That's all. I'm not fighting anybody!
Token弃权！
Token forefits!
白人胜了！白人胜了!
Whites win! Whites win!
大家看 种族战阵再次结束！ 白人再次胜利！
Race war is over again, everybody! Whites won again!
我想真诚地深深地道歉 为我在财富轮盘上说了"N"字
I want to apologize deeply and sincerely for using the "N" word on Wheel of Fortune.
我想向你保证 我并不是种族分子 Jackson神父
And I want to assure you that I'm not a racist, reverend Jackson.
你要解的字谜是“你讨厌的人”
The puzzle you were solving was: "People who annoy you?"
嗯 我是说 难道其他人 都想的是Naggers吗？是吧？
Well, like anybody else thought it was naggers, I mean, right?
Marsh先生 你需要花点时间 了解一下非裔美国人的文化
Mr. Marsh, you need to take time to understand African-American culture.
参观黑人博物馆 观看黑人表演者和艺术家
Visit black museums, see black performers and artists.
哦 我会的 我很支持非裔美国人
Oh, I will. I'm really down with African-Americans.
-你真的想道歉吗？你确定吗？ -是的 绝对是
Do you really want to apologize? Are you sure? - Yes, absolutely.
很好 如果你想道歉 我会接受
Very well. If you want to apologize. I will accept.
哦 谢谢你 Jackson先生 谢谢你
Oh, thank you, Mr. Jackson. Thank you.
-Brian 拍一张Marsh先生道歉的照片 -准备好了 先生
Brian, get a picture of Mr. Marsh apologizing. - Ready to go, sir.
-亲这边 -啊？
Kiss it. - Uh?
道歉 亲这边
Apologize. Kiss it.
-你要我亲你的-- -没错 道歉啊
You want me to kiss your- - That's right, apologize.
啊 好吧 我 呃...
Ah, okay. I'll uh...
让我听听 呃...
Let's hear uh...
道歉啊
Apologize.
嗨 Token 我只想让你知道 现在所有事都解决了
Hey, Token, I just wanted to let you know, that everything is cool now.
我爸爸向Jackson神父道歉了
My dad apologized to Jesse Jackson.
哦 我明白了 那我现在应该感觉好多了？
Oh, I see. So I'm supposed to feel all better now?
-嗯 对啊 -你就是不明白 Stan
Well, yeah. - You just don't get it, Stan.
老兄 Jackson神父说没事了
Dude, Jesse Jackson said it's okay.
Jackson神父不是黑人皇帝
Jesse Jackson is not the emporer of black people!
他告诉我爸爸他是
He told my dad he was.
今天我们会有一位嘉宾演讲者 跟我们谈谈语言的敏感和力量
Today we are going to have a guest speaker talk to us about sensitivity and the power of words.
马上你们会见到David Nelson博士
In a moment, you will meet Dr. David Nelson.
他有着被恶意毁谤的第一手经验
Who has firsthand experience in overcoming slander,
因为David自己就是小型人
because David is himself a little person.
有谁知道"小型人"是什么意思？
Who knows what a little person is?
-那边那位同学 -侏儒？
Yes, over there? - A midget?
不太对 那个词事实上被认为是具有冒犯性的
Not exactly. That term is actually considered offensive.
这就是为什么Nelson博士在学校作巡回演讲
And that's why Dr. Nelson goes from school to school
他让我们都思考我们所说的
getting us all to think about what we say.
他有两个博士学位 发表六本著作 让我们欢迎David Nelson
He has two Ph. D.'s and has published six books. Please welcome David Nelson!
早上好 学生们 你们今天感觉如何？
Good morning, students. How are we all feeling today?
我向跟你们分享一下我所有的--
I would like to share with you all my-
不 老兄 他妈的不会吧
No, dude! No, fucking way!
老兄
Dude.
那些词就像子弹 如果你--
That words are like bullets and if you give-
别 别 别
Just stop, stop, stop!
-Eric 安静 -不 不 没关系
Eric, be quiet. - No, no, it's okay.
他很快就会没劲了
He will run out of steam here pretty soon.
看看 看看 他们还给他穿小西装！
Look, look, look! They put a little suit on him!
所以我跟我老婆讲
So I said to my wife:
"你叫我杀该死的蟑螂 别因为我弄乱屋子就冲我大喊大叫"
"You told me to kill the damn cockroach, don't yell at me for making a mess!"
今晚我们观众不少 现在 有多少人真的从科罗拉多来？
We got a great crowd here tonight. Now, how many people here are actually from Colorado?
礼拜五晚没事做 只能来喜剧俱乐部 啊？
Got nothing better to do on a friday night than to go to a comedy club, uh?
嘿 我认识你吗？
Hey, don't I know you from somewhere?
对 我认识你 你就是那个在财富轮盘说黑鬼的家伙
Yeah, I know you. You're the guy that said nigger on Wheel of Fortune!
大家快看 这就是那个黑鬼男
Look, everybody, it's the nigger guy.
嗨 是他
Hey, it is him.
哦 俱乐部来了明星 大家向黑鬼男挥手 说 “嗨 黑鬼男”
Oh, we got a star in the club. Everyone wave to the nigger guy, say "Hi, nigger guy."
嗨 黑鬼男！
Hi, nigger guy!
没关系 黑鬼男 你知道我们只是玩玩
That's allright, nigger guy, you know we just playing.
是的 没关系
Yeah. No problem.
近来你们看见过车里的导航系统吗？
Have y'all seen these navigation systems in these cars, these days?
该死的玩意儿 好像他们缺了牛B太空坚果似的 （牛B太空坚果是70年代一部电视剧）
Damn things look like they're right out of space nuts.
也许黑鬼男有 你有的 黑鬼男？
Maybe nigger guy has one, you got one, nigger guy?
嗨 Patty 快看 是那个黑鬼男
Hey, look, Patty. It's that nigger guy.
黑鬼男 黑鬼男
Nigger guy, nigger guy.
嗨 你觉得你在干什么？
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
我只想买点阿司匹林
I just need some aspirin.
这个店不欢迎你 黑鬼男
You aren't welcome in this store, nigger guy.
好吧
Fine.
Victoria校长 我很担心一个学生的行为
Principal Victoria, I'm very concerned about the behavior of one of your students.
是的 对Eric Cartman的行为我们道歉 Nelson先生 我们很难过
Yes, we apologize for Eric Cartman's behavior, Mr. Nelson. We feel terrible.
为什么？我不觉得难过 我根本没放在心上
Why? I don't feel terrible. It doesn't bother me at all.
言语就像子弹 我让它们从我身体穿过
Words are like bullets and I let them pass right through me.
我知道 跟这位Eric Cartman 单独相处一段时间
I just know that with some one-on-one time together with this Eric Cartman.
我有机会改变他的想法
I have a chance to change the way he thinks.
最好你就此算了 好吗？
It might be best if you just let it go, OK?
你不明白 你看 言语像子弹
You don't understand. You see, words are like bullets.
-如果你拿走火药-- -对对 我们明白了 Nelson先生
And if you take away the gun powder- - Yeah, yeah, we get it, Mr. Nelson.
很好 Nelson先生 Stacy 去把Eric Cartman叫进来
Very well, Mr. Nelson. Stacy, go ahead and send in Eric Cartman.
Eric Nelson先生很关注你对小型人的态度
Eric, Mr. Nelson is concerned about how you respond to little people.
是不是我伤害了他的“小型感情”？
Did I hurt his little feelings?
你知道 你以为你有能力让我觉得不舒服
You know, you think you have the power to make me insecure.
但其实你的言语毫无力量
But your words are actually completely powerless.
我们应该找8个这个 把他们打扮成小海狸 是吧？
We should get like eight of these. We can dress them all up like little beavers, right?
然后把他们放在池塘里 看看他们能不能造出来水坝
And then put them in a pond and see if they build a dam!
你看 无论你说什么 我仍然屹立不倒
You see, no matter what you say, I'm still standing.
几乎没有
Barely!
不管你有什么举动 我都能扛过去
No matter how you act, I can rise above it.
扛过去 哈哈 明白吗？
Rise above it. Get it?
-闭上你的鸟嘴！ -Nelson先生！
Shut your fucking mouth! - Mr. Nelson!
他没有得逞 我刚才只是开玩笑
He didn't get to me. I was just joking.
看看他的脸变得通红 他好像个小草莓啊
Look, look how it's face gets all red. He's like a little strawberry.
恶毒之言语 如影又随形
words with venom, words that bind.
言语似武器 遮蔽我心灵
words used like weapons to cloud my mind.
我是一个人 我也有尊严
I'm a person, I'm a man
无论努力再三
but no matter how hard I try
人们只会说 "嗨 这是黑鬼男"
people just say: "Hey, there goes that nigger guy."
处处皆一样 难逃我恶名
everywhere I go it's always the same, I can't get away from that terrible name.
嗨 黑鬼男 黑鬼男 黑鬼男 停！
hey, nigger guy, nigger guy, nigger guy stop!
来吧
now go.
叫我黑鬼男 仇恨我来担 想来放到我？ 哦 你已一步慢
call me nigger guy, fill me with your hate, try to bring me down, oh, you're to late.
打击至如斯 我梦仍未死
someone just beat you to it, but my dream will not die.
期盼有一天 不再是黑鬼男
to be thought of as more, than just nigger guy.
敬礼
Respect.
Token 嗨 等等
Token, hey, wait up.
我只想说 我现在明白了
I just wanted to say, I get it now.
你知道 自从那天那个小型人在集会上演讲以后
You know, after that little person talked at that assembly the other day.
我明白有人说“N”字的时候你是什么感受
I understand how you feel about somebody saying the "N" word.
就是说...黑人是侏儒喽？
So... black people are midgets?
该死的
Goddammit!
对不起 请往这边 我需要所有学生到我这边
Excuse me, over here please. I need all students to join me over here.
我叫你们来 是因为是时候我们给 Eric Cartman上一课了 一劳永逸
I've called you here because it's time that we taught Eric Cartman a lesson, once and for all.
Eric马上就会到 当他走过那道门时
And in a few seconds Eric will be sent in, when we walk through that door.
我要你们所有人同时向他喊 "你好 肥男"
I want you all at the same time to yell, "Hello, fatso."
我觉得这不是好主意 先生
I don't think that's a very good idea, sir.
他必须得到教训 你明白吗 言语就像子弹
He has to learn his lesson, you see, words are like bullets.
好吧 好吧 他来了
Allright, allright, here he comes.
早晨好 肥男
Good morning fatso!
嗨 这他妈什么意思？ 你以为这他妈的很有趣？
Hey, what the hell is that? You think that's fucking funny?
Kyle 是你让大家这么做的？ 我猜就是你 他妈的怎么回事？
Kyle, did you put everybody up to this. I bet you did, what the hell is going on?!
现在你也尝到滋味了
Now you know how it feels.
到你头上你也不乐意 对吧？
You didn't like it when the tables were turned, did you?
好啊 好啊 是哪个天才给他穿小背带裤的？
Allright, allright, who is the freaking genius who dressed up it in little suspenders.
Clyde是你吗？
Clyde, was that you?
我荣幸地宣布...
And so it is my honor...
Randy Marsh非裔美国人 奖学金基金会今天成立
to announce today the Randy Marsh African-American scholarship foundation.
我希望这个基金会将证明...
It is my hope that this foundation will prove...
我对非裔美国学生教育的承诺
my commitment to the education of African-American students.
以及一次性洗刷掉我“黑鬼男”的身份
And erase, once and for all my identity as the nigger guy.
你们真的...
You really...
你们真的不了解你过去的污点被 一次次提起是多么痛苦
you really don't know how hard it is to be constantly reminded of something
lame that happened in your past.
我的意思是 我... 只想忘却财富轮盘上发生的那一幕 你知道
I mean I... just wanna move on from what happened on Wheel of Fortune, you know.
当人们叫你黑鬼男...
When people call me nigger guy...
就像他们翻开我历史上沉痛的一章
they're bringing up a painfull chapter of my history
负面影响一直伴随着我
and the negativity that went along with it.
你们不能想象这是怎样的感受
You just, you can't imagine how that feels.
这个黑鬼男是认真的吗？
Is this nigger guy serious?
无论如何 今天对我们所有人来说 都是新的开始 谢谢你们！
Anyway, here is to a new start for us all, thank you!
嗨 Skeeter快看 这是电视上那个家伙
Hey, look, Skeeter, that's that guy from the tv.
哈 哈 哈 咱们看见黑鬼男了
Well, well, well. Looks like we got ourselves a nigger guy.
喔！
Whoa !
你往哪儿跑啊 黑鬼男？
Where you going, nigger guy?
-求你了 我不想惹麻烦 -哦 你已经有麻烦了...
Please, I don't want any trouble. - Well, you got trouble!
当你一开始在财富轮盘上 决定侮辱整个种族的时候
When you first decided to slander an entire race of people on Wheel of Fortune.
耶 你喜欢开少数民族的玩笑吗 黑鬼男？
Yeah, you like making fun of minorities, nigger guy?
对社会无知分子 我们可不手软
We don't take kindly to social ignorance.
说得好 Skeeter 说得好
You tell him Skeeter, you tell him!
-你们要什么？ -我们要什么？
What do you want? - What do we want?
我们要生活在一个世界 这个世界上没有人像你一样不能容忍非裔美国人
We want to live in a world without people like you who are intolerant of African-Americans.
放过他
Leave him alone.
嗨 他是另一个黑鬼男
Hey, that's that other nigger guy.
是那个在Seinfeld上说了N次"N"字的家伙 （Seinfeld是著名情景喜剧）
That's the guy from Seinfeld used the "N" word a whole bunch of times.
Michael Richards 狗娘养的
Michael richards, well, son of a bitch.
咱们今天运气不错 一下子干掉两个黑鬼男
Looks like it's our lucky day, we done got us two nigger guys.
是三个
Make that three.
-Mark Fuhrman -谁？
Mark Fuhrman. - Who?
他在辛普森案上说了"N"字
He done said the "N" word in the O.J. case.
这算什么？黑鬼男大聚会？
What is this a nigger guy convention?
我们不再逆来顺受了
We aren't being pushed around anymore.
离开!
Leave!
算了 Skeeter 这些黑鬼男不值得我们惹麻烦
Come on, Skeeter, these nigger guys ain't worth our trouble.
该死的黑鬼男 我们会回来的！
Damn nigger guys, we will be back!
你最好跟我们一起
You better come with us.
进来 Marsh先生 我们给你冲点咖啡
Come on in, Mr. Marsh, we'll make you coffee.
这是怎么回事？
What's going on here?
看到新闻后 我们一直跟进你的消息
We've been following your story since we first saw it on the news.
别担心 你现在跟朋友在一起
Don't worry, you're with friends now.
Dale在工作中用"N"字讲了个种族笑话
Dale here used the "N" word in a racial joke at work.
Scott用"N"字的复数 来指一群破坏他篱笆的园丁
Scott used the plural "N" word to refer to a group of gardeners who broke his fence.
他们是墨西哥人 我只是讽刺一下
They were Mexicans, I was being ironic.
我们都和你一样
We're all just like you.
不 不 不 对不起 我跟你们不一样
No, no, no, I'm sorry, but I'm not like you.
我只是错口说了"N"字 为了赢钱而已
I just said the "N" word by mistake to win money.
我也犯了错 我只是想搞搞笑
I made a mistake to, I was trying to be funny!
我很郁闷 以为我能收获一阵大笑呢
I got frustrated and thought I would get some shock laughs.
我只是...不是个好的喜剧演员而已 如果你想知道真相的话
I'm just... not that good of an comedian if you wanna know the real truth.
你当着黑人的面说"N"字 那可比我严重多了
You said the "N" word to a black man's face. That's way worse than what I did.
你真以为有区别吗？
You really think that matters?
你真以为人们会看到不同吗？
You really think all those people out there see a difference?
哦 他们可能会将你的种族蔑称视为意外 甚至他们可能笑笑
Oh, they might see your racial slur was more accidental, they might even laugh about it.
但到最后 对他们来说 你只不过是另一个黑鬼男
But at the end of the day, all you are to them is just an another damn nigger guy.
哦 你不爽了 对吧？
Oh, you don't like that, do you?
-不爽 -Randy 我们想你加入我们
No. - Randy, we want you to join us.
我们有个计划可以一劳永逸的解决问题
We have a plan to make this all go away, once and for all.
听着 Token 我尽我所能来纠正事情
Now, look, token. I've done everything I can to make this right.
你没道理还在生气
You have no reason to still be mad.
我有的是理由生气 你就是不明白
I have every reason to be mad. You just don't get it.
我不能为我爸爸做点事情负责任
I'm not responsible for what my dad did.
你不用 但你也不能假装什么都没发生
No, but you can't just pretend it never happened either.
-你到底要我怎样？ -什么也不要
What the hell do you want from me? - Nothing.
-那就别再生气 -不！
Then stop being mad. - No!
伙计们 伙计们 快来 Cartman要跟侏儒打架
Fellas, fellas, come quick! Cartman is gonna fight the midget!
嗨 快打啊
Hey, come on now!
老兄 你真想打？很明显这家伙是空手道黑带
Dude, you sure you wanna do this? Apparently this guy has a black belt in karate.
侏儒而已 老兄
It's a midget, dude.
学生们 我会把这个小子打得屁滚尿流 来证明一点
Students, I am going to beat the crap out of this kid to prove a point.
不 不 老兄 不能说话 这不公平 我会笑得太多的
No, no, dude, it can't talk. That isn't fair, I'll laugh to much.
参议员们 我知道 美国人通常不禁用词
Senators, I know it's not normally considered American to ban words.
但有一个贬义词造成诸多伤害
But there is one slur that's caused so much damage...
我们相信它最终应该被定为非法
that we believe it should finally be made illegal.
当然 我是说的是“黑鬼男”这个词
I'm talking of course about the term nigger guy.
黑鬼男？
Nigger-guy?
两个字分开使用是无害的 但合在一起...
Two words which by themselves can be harmless, but which together...
-就构成了言语上的仇恨导弹 -对 说得对
form a verbal missile of hate. - Yeah, that's right.
哦 当然 有人只是随便一说
Oh, sure, some people just use the term in guest.
讲一两个黑鬼男笑话 觉得没什么大不了
Tell a nigger guy joke or two, thinking it's no big deal.
但他们没意识到 这将导致这个词 被人们用来当作使用暴力的借口
But they don't realise it can lead to people using the term as an excuse for violence.
该死的黑鬼男想玩政治正确了
Goddamn nigger guy is trying to be all political right now.
参议员们 我承认我是不是 会有一些轻微的种族主义思维
Senators, I've learned to admit I'm capable of having slightly racist thoughts once in a while.
有任何人敢说他从来没有吗？
Can anybody say they never do?
需要多长时间所有人都被叫做黑鬼男呢？
How long will it be, before you're all called nigger guys?
等一下 你在说"黑鬼男"可能成为...
Hold on a second, are you suggesting that nigger guy could become
指代所有白人的贬义词？
a slur that refers to all white people?
我绝对不是黑鬼男 我从没有任何种族主义思维
I'm certainly not a nigger guy, I've never thought a racist thought.
哦 得了吧 你是华盛顿最大的黑鬼男
Oh, come on, you're the biggest nigger guy in Washington.
Marsh先生 我们明白你们提案的重要性了
Mr. Marsh, we see now the importance of your bill.
赞成禁用"黑鬼男"词的人
All those in favor to ban the term nigger guy.
-赞成 -反对？
Aye. - Opposed?
反对
Nay.
动议通过了！
The motion is passed!
-好的 -好的
Allright! - Allright!
我们做到了！
We did it!
美国历史上第一次 一个词被正式禁用
For the first time in American history a word has been officially banned from use.
从现在起 如果有人使用"黑鬼"这个字
From now on, if a person uses the word nigger
它必须与"男"这个字相隔至少7个字
it must be atleast seven words away from the word guy.
Tom 看来这股"黑鬼男"传染病结束了 哦 妈的 我说了 是吧？
Tom, it appears that the nigger guy epidemic is over. Oh, dammit, I said it, didn't I?
好 好 你赢了！
Okay, okay, you win!
-叫叔叔 -叔叔
Say uncle! - Uncle!
-现在说"Carol Anne别挂了" -Carol Anne别挂了
Now say, Carol Anne don't go into the light. - Carol Anne don't go into the light.
现在你们都明白了...
There, now you all see...
我没有受限于我的体型
that I am not limited by my size!
我已经证明了我的观点 我这儿的任务完成了
I have proven my point. My work here is done.
-他的观点是什么？ -我不知道
What was his point? - I have no idea.
-老兄 我没弄明白 -我也不明白
Dude, I don't get it. - I don't get it either.
等一下 就着这个 我不明白
Wait a minute. That's it. I don't get it.
你没看出来吗 Kyle？ 我不明白
Don't you see, Kyle? I don't get it!
Token 我现在明白了 我不明白
Token, I get it now. I don't get it.
我试图说我理解你的感受 但我永远不会理解
I've been trying to say that I understand how you feel, but I'll never understand.
我永远不会真正理解 当有人说"N"字的时候 一个黑人的感受
I'm never really get how it feels for a black person to have somebody use the "N" word.
我不明白
I don't get it.
-现在你明白了Stan -是的 我完全不明白
Now you get it, Stan. - Yeah, I totally don't get it.
谢谢你 老兄
Thanks, dude.
翻译:sansanfeng @ 1000fr.com 校对:sansanfeng @ 1000fr.com
Sranscipt: muter Sync: muter
双语合成 Lv&daisy